maturescam.com 2009-03-23

# Free Live Sex - Hot Live Sex Shows!... MaturesCam..

**Need help?**

You are very important to us and we strive to provide You with world class Customer Service. Customer Service agents are standing by 24 hours a day, 7 days a week, in order to meet Your needs. You may contact them online at the Customer Support chatroom or via e-mail by filling out the form below. 

For online assistance, visit our customer support chatroom. 

Please be advised that the billing operation is being handled by  Support from now on. If You have questions about billing, please call  at: (+351) 291 003 610 ** **

Payment processor's consumer support::

Please fill out the form with correct data. All fields are required! Please be advised that our Support Team is available only in English! 

**Q - When I've given my credit-card information to similar sites in the past, they abused it.  
How do I know I can trust You? **   
A - MaturesCam is one of the fastest-growing web-conferencing and videochat services on the internet. 

With millions of registered users and over 9,000 registered video chathosts, both numbers growing every day, and with participation from more than 50 different countries. 

No company online or offline could ever hope to achieve that degree of success by engaging in abusive practices or by taking advantage of its customers. 

At MaturesCam, the Customer is King. You are king. 

We are extremely proud of our record for excellence in customer service. 

**Q - How do I know my personal information is safe on Your servers? What about hackers?**   
A - Your registration information is always safe from hackers. 

All elements of the registration form (including this very message) are SSL-encrypted via Verisign digital certificates for Your complete and total safety (look for the "closed padlock" icon when using Internet Explorer/AOL/Netscape or similar browsers). 

Since the beginning of our operation, 2001, our encrypted and firewall-protected systems have never suffered even a single serious security breach. 

**Q - If I fill out the form, am I going to get slammed with junk e-mail from 3rd parties?**   
A - Perhaps with other internet services, but never with MaturesCam. 

MaturesCam never shares or sells Your registration information, including Your e-mail address, with outside parties. 

Of course, if You contact any of MaturesCam's 9,000+ videochat hosts and exchange Your contact information with a chathost, we can't prevent that chathost from sending You e-mail, but that is Your decision -- MaturesCam never makes that decision for You. 

MaturesCam is a "Scam-Free Zone". 

What's that? If You've spent much time surfing the web, especially those sites that offer adult-oriented areas, You've learned (probably the hard way) not to give Your credit-card number or other financial information to a website unless You're positive Your personal and financial information won't be misused or abused by hackers or by anyone else (including the site itself). 

First, on MaturesCam, Your membership information is always safe from hackers. All elements of the registration form are SSL-encrypted via Verisign digital certificates for Your complete and total safety (look for the "closed padlock" icon when using Internet Explorer/AOL/Netscape or similar browsers). Moreover, ever since our first day of operation on the internet (we've been online since the earliest days of the web), our encrypted and firewall-protected systems have never suffered even a single serious security incident. 

Second, at MaturesCam, any personal information collected from You is kept strictly confidential and is for the limited purpose of identity verification to protect MaturesCam from abusive behavior. (E-commerce-enabled Chat services occasionally attract user misconduct such as identity theft, spam and other abuses. 

MaturesCam undertakes responsible measures to verify Your identity, including matching Your registration information against available verification databases and services. Of course, Your privacy is respected and protected at all times). Any payment information collected will never be used to charge You for anything, unless You specifically authorize us to. You'll never be burned by MaturesCam. Ever. Other sites bury the fees and terms in the fine print (and some don't even care to mention them). But our plain-English Terms of Service explains in the first paragraph how it all works. 

**How MaturesCam Protects Your Privacy?**

\- A We **NEVER** sell, rent or share Your personal information or e-mail address with any other party!   
\- We may send You occasional promotional e-mails, and every e-mail will contain an unsubscribe option.   
\- Your personal information is **NEVER** stored on MaturesCam.com's server, so it cannot be stolen by hackers. 

Not only we do respect Your privacy, we protect Your privacy!!!

MaturesCam is occasionally contacted by third parties who, for marketing purposes, want to purchase our mailing list and other sensitive customer information derived from our database. Although there is no law forbidding MaturesCam from selling such information, the trading of which is an extremely lucrative business, MaturesCam is serious in its commitment to protecting Your personal privacy. We have never sold such personal information about our customers to outside parties -- not even once -- and we never will. 

**As a general rule, MaturesCam collects only three kinds of information about You:**

**1.** Information that You voluntarily provide to us or authorize us to view, such as Your name, address, credit-card and other account information as submitted on the MaturesCam Membership Submission Form. 

**2.** "Log information" about the areas of MaturesCam that You visit, that are accessible from the general internet environment. 

**3.** Private correspondence, such as the contents of telephone conversations, chat client logs, faxes or letters to MaturesCam staff, e-mail messages to performers or MaturesCam staff, performer chat client logs. 

**Log information bears greater explanation:**

Log information typically consists of such things as Your browser type (i.e., Netscape or MSIE), Your IP address (i.e., 102.316.52.11), the domain name from which You are visiting MaturesCam (i.e., "aol.com"), and the pages of MaturesCam that You visit. Like all internet services, we analyze our log files to better understand which areas of MaturesCam are more popular than others. And like most other large-scale internet properties, we also use this information to "customize" the MaturesCam experience to match Your tastes. For example, if You first visit MaturesCam by searching an internet portal for a search term such as "voyeur" and clicking upon an MaturesCam banner or link, MaturesCam may set a "cookie" on Your computer which records the term as a "search preference" (Note: Everyday log-analysis programs such as WebTrends include such tracking of keyword-specific traffic as a regular feature - indeed, using such tools, the administrators of most websites on earth track traffic originating from search engines by searched keyword).   
Later, as You navigate through MaturesCam, You will likely observe that the content You see on MaturesCam tends to be tailored to match Your recorded search preference. Note: such cookies are "secure" in that they cannot be read by other internet companies, but can only be read by the web site which placed the cookie on Your computer.

MaturesCam also uses Your recorded "search preference" information to better target and allocate marketing expenditures.   
For example, if MaturesCam learns that, in aggregate, individuals who search portals for terms such as "voyeur" are more likely to purchase goods and services from MaturesCam than individuals who search for terms such as "livecams", MaturesCam may allocate greater portions of its marketing budget to targeting the former group, and a smaller portion of its budget to target the latter group. By optimizing marketing strategies in this manner, MaturesCam has more disposable capital that can be deployed toward development efforts which improve the MaturesCam platform and provide a richer customer experience for all. 

Speaking of cookies, another kind of cookie that MaturesCam sets is an "identification cookie". This cookie is written whenever You successfully use Your login and password to access a restricted area of MaturesCam; the identification cookie is available only to individuals who have already been verified as adults, via MaturesCam's verification procedures. When MaturesCam's servers observe this identification cookie on Your computer, they recognize You and therefore might deliver unmodified content as opposed to modified content - in effect, another form of customized content tailored to suit Your indicated preferences. 

Another question that might concern You: "Does MaturesCam outsource to other companies any privacy-sensitive functions such as management of its e-mail newsletter system, web hosting, or its e-commerce platform?" Because MaturesCam is committed to safeguarding the integrity of Your personal information, we have elected to not use such services, despite the fact that they are reasonably-priced and simplify the management task of running a large and complex website operation. 

By entering this website, You accept the following agreement: 

This website contains adult-oriented material that may be offensive to, or illegal for some readers.   
This website also contains Explicit Adult Nudity. If You are offended by this type of material then  DO NOT ENTER THIS SITE. 

Please note that this site contains sexually oriented adult material intended for individuals 18 Years (21 in some areas, please check local regulations) or older. If You are not over 18 Years of age (21 in some areas, please check local regulations), If adult material offends You or if You are accessing this site from any country or locale where adult material is specifically prohibited by law, then  DO NOT ENTER THIS SITE. 

This website is an adult entertainment and educational resource not designed to promote prurient interests.   
MaturesCam does not warrant the information presented here. Furthermore, a listing is not to be construed as any type of implied endorsement for the authors or services of the listed pages or the information contained thereon. 

To protect our users from viewing adult-oriented material without their consent, MaturesCam requires You to read and certify the following statements. 

NOTE: Do not continue unless You know Your local obscenity laws, and furthermore know that they do  
not prohibit the viewing of adult material.   
**By accepting this agreement, I certify the following:**

  1. I am at least eighteen (18) years old (21 in some areas, please check local regulations).
  2. The sexually explicit material I am buying and/or viewing is for my own personal use and I will never expose minors to said material.
  3. I believe that, as an adult, I have the unalienable right to read and/or view any type of material that I choose and that the material and images contained in this website are not obscene or offensive in any way, nor could ever be construed to be obscene or offensive.
  4. The viewing, reading, and downloading of the material and images in this website do not violate the community standards of my street, village, city, town, county, state, province, or country.
  5. That I am wholly liable for any false disclosures and responsible for any legal ramifications that may arise from viewing, reading, or downloading of material and images contained within this website and that MaturesCam, and its affiliates cannot be held responsible for any legal ramifications that may arise as a result of fraudulent entry into, or use of, this website and/or material contain herein
  6. I hereby acknowledge and agree that placing any advertisement or link on this website or on any page of this website - without the prior written consent of MaturesCam.com - is forbidden and may result the infringement of rights and therefore a legal procedure.

This warning page constitutes a legal Agreement between MaturesCam.com and Yourself, as well as any business entity of which You have any legal or equitable interest. If any portion of this Agreement is deemed unenforceable by a Court of competent jurisdiction, it shall not affect the enforceability of the other portions of this Agreement.   
We would like to inform You, for ALL legal statements, statutory declarations made by MaturesCam.com and it's Owner, and can be found on the site (such as our Privacy Policy, Terms & Conditions, Spam & Refund Policy, the Agreements, Documents for the Studios, Performers) we can ONLY take the ENGLISH version as a basis and underlying! We DO NOT accept any kind of legal claims, or other complaints for the misunderstandings as a result of the mistranslations!
